{
    "subject": "Lucien_Hubbard",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Rose-Marie__1928_film_",
    "human_readable": "Lucien Hubbard directed the film Rose-Marie (1928).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8939725160598755,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Lucien Hubbard."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8686252236366272,
            "question": "Who directed the film Rose-Marie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.852952241897583,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Lucien Hubbard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.736125648021698,
            "question": "Were there any famous actors involved in Rose-Marie (1928)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7327418923377991,
            "question": "Was Lucien Hubbard involved in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7063223123550415,
            "question": "What year was the film Rose-Marie released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6580092906951904,
            "question": "How popular was Rose-Marie (1928) upon its release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6504731178283691,
            "question": "What genre was Rose-Marie (1928) likely to belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5677776336669922,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other films directed by Lucien Hubbard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4994570016860962,
            "question": "What is the subject matter of the film Rose-Marie?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lucien Hubbard directed the film Rose-Marie (1928).",
            "html": "yago_11382_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide examples of other films directed by Lucien Hubbard?",
            "html": "yago_11382_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre was Rose-Marie (1928) likely to belong to?",
            "html": "yago_11382_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How popular was Rose-Marie (1928) upon its release?",
            "html": "yago_11382_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11382_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11382_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11382_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11382_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11382_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11382_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11382_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11382_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11382_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11382_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that there was a film called Rose-Marie released in 1928, and according to one of the documents, this film was directed by Lucien Hubbard. The context information supports this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Lucien Hubbard directed the 1928 film adaptation of \"Rose-Marie,\" which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}